Where is everyone?
Campsite!
Yeah!
# Over the chute with you
♪ Hot summer's over forever ♪
Ihrer
않는다
Boo boo say, ah ah ah ah
Dum-dum, I'm working too hard, too hard, too hard, too fast, too fast, too fast
Boo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo
Burner, why are you doing so well
Burner!
What's the next event?
I'll post it on the official Twitter page.
The team with the most retweets and likes from fans will win.
The team with the most likes will win.
You've got 30 minutes to come up with a great photo for each team.
I'm looking for a good photo for each team to think about and take a good picture
I'm going to live with the message, and I'm not going to post it all in one shot.
I'm not just posting this in one shot... but three at once!
I had it!
Let's do it! Let's try it again!
Cute, but cute!
Let's do some more tests!Let's make it a little more of a test.
It's going to be a test.
It's not even on the stone.
It's only in this sand or something.
I'm sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'll take a look.
I'll take a look.
You want to hold the chopping board?
What? The frying pan and the cutting board.
This one's in trouble.
Cutting board and frying pan.
You can grab the end here if you want.
You want to take that one? That's it.
What? You're cooking? He's like, "I'm cooking.
Okay, I'll just try it out for one shot.
Wow! Oh, man, isn't this so good?
Isn't it great?
Now we just need to decide on our poms.
No, really.
Let's go.
Wow, but if Amuku was here...
I'm sure we'd get something interesting.
I'm sure it would.
It's a little frustrating.It's a little frustrating.
I bet he's funny.
Next!
I'm sorry!
I know!
Ready?
Yes!
It's so good! It's so good, but...
I don't know what to say.
It's good, right?
It's good, isn't it?
I'm in playtime.
With this system?
Look at this.
Okay, bye.
I'll be back in a minute.
Stand still.
But it's water.
We know it's water.
And the other clues...
Here we go.
Cheese!
Let's try one more time.
Cheese.
But it's only one piece, right?But it's one of your best, right?
Yes, it's the best one I've ever made.
It's like someone found a rock.
And the top part is so natural.
Wait a minute. It's too heart-shaped.
It's so good! It's so good!
Let's do this.
Wait, here it is.
More, more, more!
Okay, so...
All the teams have finished shooting.
Yay!
But, I have to say, everyone seems pretty confident about this.
That's for sure.
That's true.
What are the results going to be like?
We'll post the results now and announce them later.
I see.
Finally.
The last one.
So, while we're waiting for the results, we'll go on to the next showdown.
What's the next showdown?
Next up is the watermelon showdown.Next will be the watermelon splitting showdown!
Wow.
This is the last one, isn't it?
That's right, the last showdown of the watermelon splitting!
Anyway, let's see which team will be the first to split the watermelon.
First, Goo. Last time, Pai.
Oh, as I thought...
Too many for me!
Number three...
Number 3, 753, and 3...
Ground!
dal
raо.
Staff, my feet hurt.
Come here!
Get out of my spot!
Hey!
Haruma, over here!
I can't see you over here!
Straight ahead!
More left!
A little more!
Straight!
Left!
Straight!Straight!
That's really big.
You said it yourself, omae ga kayakayakayakayakayakayakayakayakayakayakay!
Two steps left.
Two steps left. One more step.
One more step to the left. One more step.
One more step back.
One step back. One step left.
Oh, hit it hard and fast right there.
A little more forward, a little more forward.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
More...
That's great!
Here are the times.
The time is...
One minute and eight seconds.
You haven't eaten.
You haven't eaten in forever.
Yum.
Tastes like victory.
Okay, bye.
Nice.
Good luck.
Wow.
Don't fall down, cousin.Don't fall down.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Shut up!
A-ha-ha-ha-ha
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Straight and straight
Straight and alone
Separate, separate, straight
split
peel
Sweetness
To this
Ippon
Maaisainai!
Right! Right! Right!
Right! Right!
Throw it, throw it!
Oh! It's over!
That's great!
Yeah!
That was one! It was one hit!
It was one and done!It was the end of one shot!
Time now.
35 seconds!
Yay!
Yeah!
What's that?
Wait a minute.
This is so funny.
This is so fun.
Wait a minute.
It's really fun.
Three boys don't make a strong team.
That's me.
The result is 3,2,1!
Congratulations!
At this point, we're in first place!
Wow!
Good luck!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
This is not a good story, don't you think? That's something.
It has to come last, don't you think?
I think it's fine.I think it's totally fine.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Um...
What do you think?
Let's make it 100 million next time.
I'd like to...
I want to eat a fancy dinner with everyone.
That's not possible.
No.
Excuse me.
Yes, yes, yes.
Um...
Really.
Make it 100 million next time.
Ha-ha-ha.
[fast forward]
Okay, so...
I'm announcing the results of the social networking sales test.
Yes!
I'm going to announce the result of the SNS Seller's Selection Examination,
I'd like to hear the results right away,
What are the results?
As for the results, the first place goes to...
Men's participation!
The second place goes to...Second place goes to...
Third place goes to...
The team of three girls.
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
The first place team is
Gorgeous Kuroge Wagyu Beef Barbecue Set
Wow!
Second place!
Who's in second place?
The second place team is
Curry, a camp staple!
Oh!
Now, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on... what about some kind of original camp menu?
You're ignoring me, aren't you?
The team of three was asked to make any camp dish they wanted for 500 yen.
They said, "Do it your own way.
I see.
But, you know, we've got 100 million points, and we've got a lot of room in our hearts.
We've got room in our hearts for one more.
Let's eat together!
Okay, so we're going to grill some meat, make curry, and cook something for 500 yen!
Let's go!Let's go!
Yeah!
I'll do it!
It's only 500 yen!
Food is ready!
I've got two guys in the middle of a shopping spree.
The two guys are shopping, and they feel guilty about going without.
They're going shopping for 500 yen.
I'm ready to eat!
I heard it's the #1 black beef there...
Let's open the package!
Ready!
Ta-da!
It's real Wagyu!
Yay!
How much do I get?
It's like the person who's a little busy helping the person who's a little busy helping the person who's a little busy.
Let's have fun!
Fun! Yay!
So, where's the engine?
What engine? What engine?
Uh...
Let's make sure it's good food.
Let's go! Ready?
Lilia!Lilia!
Straw, straw!
Wamon-dokare!
I'm going to say "Hajimeshare!
We're going to use all of these, right?
Okay, I'm cooking the rice.
Yay! I'm here for the rice.
You want it all cooked?
And I can put this in here?
Yeah, just make sure it's tight.
Let's see.
No. 4 is supposed to make two cups of this.
So 4, 4, 4, 4, 12 is enough?
Yes, yes, yes.
I live on 100 grams.
I'm sorry.
I live here with two other people, but I don't use the right amount.
I've never done it before.
I don't have any lightweight cups at home.
I really don't have any.
I have a woman's touch.
How cool!
You put it on low heat at first.
When it spills, put it on high.
Is that too much to ask?Is this too much?
Is this adjustment too much?
Thank you for watching!
Oh, I'm scared of three more!
But you put it so beautifully!
You're so good!
You're a good cook!
I'm in the process of cutting this.
Okay, so...
We spent 500 yen to buy something.
We'll spend 500 yen to buy something.
And then come back over there
We're going to cook.
Yes, sir.
Hey, we've already decided.
Camping? I mean, this is what I'm talking about.
We'll cook together.
Okay, I'm going to go buy some now!
Ready!
Yes, I bought it!
I bought it!
I managed to keep it within 500 yen!
That was a little close.
Only 27 yen left!
What a surprise, I had to pay for the bag too...What a surprise to learn that it also costs money for the bag.
I'm sure it was included in the calculation.
I'm going to take this with me to everyone!
I'm going to make this.
It's pretty scary.
Why one hand?
What?
I'm sure.
You're right.
Like this?
It's easier this way.
I'm losing a lot of onions.
Then put your thumb on it.
I'll cut along this line.
I see.
Okay.
Here it comes.
I think I have a knack for this.
Half is fine?
Half is fine.
What?
It's hot!
In!
Well, let's make this one stronger.Then let's make this one stronger.
Yeah!
Just do it right. No more carrots.
Hey, do you have any Chetik, carrots?
Pretty thin?
Just a slice.
It's sliced in rounds.
What am I doing?
Let's have something thicker.
Fire.
Oh, it smells so good!
Oh, I'm so excited!
Yay!
Yay, it's all over at once!
Palma-sensei taught me a lot!
Thank you for teaching me!
I'm home!
The fan is so useful!
Hey.
Hey! Wait!
I have one of my own.
I thought we didn't have one, but I found this and it's great!
What did you get me?
We all went to the river.They all went to that river.
We're going, too?
We went to get rocks... rocks.
Traitor.
What?
What traitor?
I wanted to come with you.
No, I couldn't find any good rocks.
I had to dive down to the river.
When the bubbles come out, I put the stone on top.
When the rice starts to burn, you take it out.
It's just a matter of taste.
I'm scared.
Too many onions.
Yuna loves onions.
I'll eat all of them.
He'll burn.
I'll put it down.
Then I'll cook it longer.
It's getting a little dry.
But it's fun to make it together.
I know, but it's not like making it with just one person.
I wouldn't make it if we didn't make it together.
That makes me happy.Eh, I'm kind of glad.
Eh, I think I might have just resonated a little.
Oh!
That's good, isn't it?
Oh, my gosh!
That's a little too much, isn't it?
Bon appétit!
If you mess it up with a scissors like this
No one will know if it's burnt or not.
Mmmm! It's so good!
Add the ingredients!
Make yakisoba!
Noodles here and
And this one here.
Bean sprouts, stir-fried vegetables
That's what's in the heaping bowl.
And I bought a winnie!
So, that's 473 yen.
3 yen is the cost of the bag.
I bought it just in time.
Cooking!
Luno-Anly Cooking begins!
It's so cool! It's really cool!
Well then, this is a good frying pan, so it slides well.
Unley, first yakisoba in your life!Mr. Ang Lee, first yakisoba in your life.
No, it's not! I'm a peculiar dish egg omelet.
Looks delicious!
Isn't this amount of food for 500 yen amazing?
It's really cosy!
I really recommend it! I really recommend it!
Yay! It's done!
Yes, so it's finished!
Yay!
When you combine the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place foods
It's a very nice camping meal!
Indeed! Thank you very much!
And welcome back, Am!
Welcome back!
Wait a minute, I'm gonna bug you so bad.
Okay, ready? Ready, set, go!
Bon appétit!
Suddenly I'm open to eating.
That's for sure.
I haven't eaten yet.
Bon appétit!
It's really good!Seriously delicious.
Wow!
Why?
No, it's good!
It's delicious!
Mmm!
Yeah!
Ogegae-umami!
It's curry, after all.
This is the first time I've made my own curry.
Curry that I make, or curry that we make together and eat together, tastes especially good!
I used to not like curry, but it tastes so good! It's so good!
It's different when you eat it with the members! It's different when you eat it with the members!
It's the best!
Is it good?
It's so good!
Really?
Yes!
Did you just get a free cup?
I've been ice cold!
Hey, what did you do! I wanted to be there!
I overheard you talking about how you'd be the funniest person in the world.
Isshin's cutting the meat!
Yay! Thank you!
Big meat!I got a big piece of meat!
Thank you!
Hey, how was your dinner today?
No, I mean, not from the food, but from the canoeing.
The gunpowder?
Yes, the gunpowder!
It was the only thing I could do.
Yeah, but seriously, the gunpowder was fun!
But really, in practice, we looked like we could handle it.
But when it came to the actual performance, I was pretty much right behind Amu.
Okay, I'll go right next! and so on.
It was so much fun!
So much fun!
So the Germans got you out of the car!
Yes!
How about that? I poured water on your head.
Really frustrating!
Really!
They're having a real meal over there!
Hey! Hey!
Can I get a normal person with skin!
Yes!
Oh, everyone!
People with skin in their eyes.The one with the skin.
What? You're in.
They're all in.
What, those two didn't make it?
No, they're not in.
What? I don't know. They're not in.
No, they're not! They were working!
You were working so hard!
You were doing your job!
No, I missed you.
You look happy! Why!
Why are you having so much fun while I was gone!
But I'm glad you're having fun!
I feel like I'm not participating in the fun, but...
We're having dinner together!
No, that's why I feel so bad about the food.
No, I don't feel that way anymore.
I wasn't so conspicuous even in the kayaku...
No, you were.
No, no, no.
You know, you know, you're an am...
And I was the one who just came to eat.
I'm the guy who came to eat after doing kayaku.
But what I realized is that...
Love One needs you, Amu.I guess that means Love One needs you, Amu.
Thank you very much.
Yes!
In the end, Amu will take care of everything.
That's what I mean!
It's no fun without you.
No, me too. I missed you guys too.
Hey!
I missed you guys too.
Hot!
No, am hot!
For the one-man zero fan.
How's it going? I knew you'd be there.
It's already a force one-man show, isn't it?
Well, it's been a little over a year now.
I am very grateful to have been able to do a force one-man show
I am very grateful for that.
And above all, it was the first time to have 9 members in the group? For the first time? Isn't it?
I think we have to show our true spirit.
I think this is a live performance that requires a lot of determination.
I really cherish every second of the show.
I want to convey my feelings to you all.
Wow!
It's just one, right? It's just one, so...It's a doggie, right? It's a doggie.
It's something special.
I can't believe this is the fourth time.
But when I think back to the last three times...
I feel like all the memories are coming back to me.
So I think of this one-one as a turning point.
I'm going to cherish it very much and do my best.
It's wonderful! It's wonderful!
Today, Am worked hard and fast, so I had a little bit of a rest afterwards.
So we had a little bit of a break after that.
But it made me realize that it's not good if one of the members
I think we all learned that it's no good if one of us is absent.
I think it's great that the nine members of one-one-one can work together as a team.
I felt that the nine members of "One One" are all "One One".
It was a great day for me.
And I think our bond has deepened a little more.
With this in mind, I'll do my best from tomorrow.
Let's do our best!
It was seriously a lot of fun and a great memory!
Well, that's the end of the camp project!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work!